<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>intrustd.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:5000/</link>
    <description>Recent content on intrustd.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:5000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Encryption is not enough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-02-14-encryption-is-not-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-02-14-encryption-is-not-enough/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five benefits of owning your data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-02-14-benefits-of-owning-your-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-02-14-benefits-of-owning-your-data/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Overview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-developer-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-developer-overview/</guid>
      <description>What is Intrustd? Intrustd is an evolving, open networking standard that creates ad-hoc virtual private networks among end-user trusted devices.
In its current form, Intrustd can be used to self-host various services. The server hosting these applications can be behind a firewall or connected directly to the internet. Intrustd uses peer-to-peer technology to communicate between the end-user browser and the Intrustd server. This allows users to own their own data, rather than trusting its storage to a separate company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/installation/2019-02-05-first-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/installation/2019-02-05-first-steps/</guid>
      <description>After Purchase After the purchase of an Intrustd appliance, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing you need to do. You can expect to receive a tracking number when your package is sent, and should receive your device a few days later.
When You Receive the Device Other than the device itself, you should receive the following with your purchase:
 The Intrustd Manual A power supply cord An Intrustd setup certificate 5 USB keys with the Intrustd logo 3 Intrustd stickers  Setup Options The easiest way to setup your device is via a computer, iPhone, or Android device connected to your local home network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation without a network</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/installation/2019-02-05-installation-without-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/installation/2019-02-05-installation-without-network/</guid>
      <description> Who should read this document The easiest way to set up an Intrustd appliance is via a computer or smart device with a browser attached to the same network. In rare situations, this is not possible. In this case, you can create a temporary globally-available access portal using the USB keys included in the box with your appliance.
TODO&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the Intrustd platform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-introduction-to-the-intrustd-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-introduction-to-the-intrustd-platform/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sample Use Cases for Intrustd Applications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-use-cases/</guid>
      <description>Purpose of Article This article seeks to enumerate sample use cases for Intrustd applications. The purpose is to determine which applications would be a good fit for Intrustd computing and which would not.
Positive Use Cases The following use-cases represent areas where applications can add significant value via ports to the Intrustd platform.
Data-driven applications Data-driven applications, like photo managers, file managers, backup solutions, are good candidates for hosting on Intrustd appliances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-01-25-what-is-intrustd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-01-25-what-is-intrustd/</guid>
      <description>title: &amp;ldquo;What is Intrustd?&amp;rdquo; date: 2019-01-25
author: Travis Athougies Intrustd is a suite of open-source programs designed to turn any Linux box into your own personal server (called appliances), accessible over the internet to those you allow, without any extra setup.
Traditionally, in order to run your own personal internet services, you either have to rent a server from a cloud computing provider or purchase a static IP from your ISP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-02-05-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/posts/2019-02-05-test/</guid>
      <description>test</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>