<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Developers on intrustd.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Developers on intrustd.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Overview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-developer-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-developer-overview/</guid>
      <description>What is Intrustd? Intrustd is an evolving, open networking standard that creates ad-hoc virtual private networks among end-user trusted devices.
In its current form, Intrustd can be used to self-host various services. The server hosting these applications can be behind a firewall or connected directly to the internet. Intrustd uses peer-to-peer technology to communicate between the end-user browser and the Intrustd server. This allows users to own their own data, rather than trusting its storage to a separate company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the Intrustd platform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-introduction-to-the-intrustd-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-introduction-to-the-intrustd-platform/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sample Use Cases for Intrustd Applications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/kb/developers/2019-02-05-use-cases/</guid>
      <description>Purpose of Article This article seeks to enumerate sample use cases for Intrustd applications. The purpose is to determine which applications would be a good fit for Intrustd computing and which would not.
Positive Use Cases The following use-cases represent areas where applications can add significant value via ports to the Intrustd platform.
Data-driven applications Data-driven applications, like photo managers, file managers, backup solutions, are good candidates for hosting on Intrustd appliances.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>